<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">IQuestor</string>


    <string name="about_us_text_res">Hello, you are being greeted by the creator of the "IQuestor" application. This application is a quest game in which you have to go through the path of a soldier, making various choices that will directly effect the continuation of the game. The main goal is to rise from private to general.</string>
    <string name="about_us_mail_res">Mail: tepanyanhayk@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="about_us_phone_res">Phone: +374 (33)–52–74-77</string>
    <string name="about_us_creator_res">Created by: Hayk Tepanyan</string>
    <string name="about_us_teacher_res">Teacher: Mikayel Elizbaryan</string>


    <string name="htp_ht_change_lang_res">1) How to change language?</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_change_lang_text_res">At the very top left, there is an icon that looks like a planet, and if you click on it, a window will appear in which you must select which language you want to change the game interface to. In Russian, or in English.</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_control_sounds_res">2) How to control sounds?</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_control_sounds_text_res">To control the volume, there is a sound icon at the top. By default, background music is turned on, but when you press this button, it will turn off and the icon will change. When pressed again, the music in the background will resume playing where it left off.</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_change_acc_res">3) How to sign-out or change account?</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_change_acc_text_res">To change or log out of your account, click on the logout button in the very top right corner. When you click on it, a menu will appear in which you need to click “yes”. You will then be taken to the registration menu.</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_about_game_res">4) Where can I read about the game?</string>
    <string name="htp_ht_about_game_text_res">In the main menu, by clicking on the bottom button that says “ABOUT US”, you will be taken to a page where everything is described in detail about the game and its developer. Also there you will find the developer’s contact information so that if you need to contact him.</string>


    <string name="act_main_play_res">PLAY</string>
    <string name="act_main_reset_progress_res">RESET PROGRESS</string>
    <string name="act_main_htp_res">HOW TO PLAY?</string>
    <string name="act_main_about_us_res">ABOUT US</string>


    <string name="startGameStory">Hello, youve turned 18 and joined the army! Your rank is Private. To rise in rank, you need to follow the right path by making various choices! (Tap here to continue)</string>
    <string name="zvaniyaStory">(All ranks - Private, Lance Corporal, Junior Sergeant, Sergeant, Staff Sergeant, Warrant Officer, Staff Warrant Officer, Junior Lieutenant, Senior Lieutenant, Captain, Major, Colonel, Major General, General.) (Tap here to continue)</string>
    <string name="nextSitRes">NEXT</string>
    <string name="nextSitRes1">FINISH</string>

    <string-array name="stories1">
        <item>The Sergeant noticed you during cleanup and praised you. The next day, you took the oath and became {rank + 1}!</item>
        <item>After cleanup, the Sergeant noticed you did nothing and reported you to the Warrant Officer. You were punished.</item>
        <item>Times have changed. Youve been sent to prison. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories2">
        <item>You accidentally bumped into the Junior Sergeant, and you were sent to prison. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You hit all the targets. The Senior Lieutenant noticed you, and you became {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>You were shot for treason against the homeland. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories3">
        <item>The Captain came and saw your actions. He thanked you, and the next day, your rank was raised. You became {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>You were all sent to prison. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>Everyone involved in the brawl was sent to prison, while you went back to the barracks.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories4">
        <item>You were taken to the border. Those who attempted to escape were shot.</item>
        <item>You were caught and shot for treason against the homeland. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You were pacified and taken to the border.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories5">
        <item>You were surrounded. All soldiers perished. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You managed to hold out for a while, and reinforcements arrived. You repelled the first attack, and your rank was raised to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>You were killed. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories6">
        <item>You marched into certain death. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You returned to the trenches, where you found mortars. You destroyed all tanks, and your rank was raised to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>The tanks passed you by, and then you successfully destroyed them from behind. You were promoted to the rank of {rank + 1}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories7">
        <item>You retreated and surrendered the land. The Major General turned out to be a traitor, and he was killed. Your rank was demoted to {rank - 1}.</item>
        <item>The Major General turned out to be a traitor, and he was killed. You were promoted twice in rank, and you became {rank + 2}.</item>
        <item>You were taken prisoner. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories8">
        <item>You only shot down 1 aircraft, and the remaining planes killed three soldiers. Your rank was demoted twice to {rank - 2}.</item>
        <item>You successfully shot down all aircraft. The mission was accomplished, so you were promoted to the rank of {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>The aircraft prevented you from leaving the shelter, and you were surrounded. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories9">
        <item>You broke through the defense but lost many soldiers. You were demoted by one rank to {rank - 1}.</item>
        <item>You managed to pass unnoticed, avoiding contact with the enemy. For such skill, you were promoted to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>The attempt to negotiate failed, and you were taken prisoner. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories10">
        <item>You successfully attacked the enemy and took their positions. You were promoted to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>The enemy proved to be stronger, and you were forced to retreat. You were demoted by one rank to {rank - 1}.</item>
        <item>Your negotiations led to a temporary truce. You were left at your current rank.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories11">
        <item>The covert mission was successful. You were promoted to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>The sabotage operation led to significant disruptions behind enemy lines. You were promoted to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>You were transferred to another direction without a change in rank.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories12">
        <item>You successfully organized the defense and repelled the enemy attack. You were promoted to {rank + 1}.</item>
        <item>You were killed during one of the operations. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You were sent to prison for disobeying orders. Defeat at the rank of {rank}.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories13">
        <item>You declined the rank of general and successfully left military life at the rank of {rank}.</item>
        <item>You became the General of the entire countrys army, bearing immense responsibility. Most importantly, you achieved your goal and became a General. Congratulations on completing the game!</item>
        <item>You unlocked the secret ending where you killed the minister, but aliens arrived and abducted you.</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="sit">
        <item name="sit1">You went to the barracks, where you need to make your bed and clean your shoes.</item>
        <item name="sit2">During the exercises, everyone was given weapons and ordered to shoot at targets.</item>
        <item name="sit3">One day, a fight broke out in the mess hall.</item>
        <item name="sit4">At night, when everyone was asleep, a military alarm was sounded. It turned out that war had begun. Youre all being taken to the border.</item>
        <item name="sit5">The enemy army is approaching. Something urgent needs to be done!</item>
        <item name="sit6">You initiated an attack, but tanks started moving against you. You need to get out of this situation.</item>
        <item name="sit7">An order came from the Major General to retreat.</item>
        <item name="sit8">Three enemy aircraft are flying in the sky. You were ordered to shoot them down at any cost.</item>
        <item name="sit9">You found yourself in a difficult situation, surrounded by enemy forces. You have to make a tough choice.</item>
        <item name="sit10">After that, you were transferred to a new direction. You will have to fight again.</item>
        <item name="sit11">After prolonged battles, you encountered an unforeseen challenge.</item>
        <item name="sit12">After successful operations and decisive actions, you caught the attention of a General. He gave you a new task.</item>
        <item name="sit13">The war is over, and you became a hero of the country. The Ministry of Defense of your country offered you the rank of general.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="choices1">
        <item>a) Do everything that needs to be done.</item>
        <item>b) Leave everything as it is and go rest.</item>
        <item>c) Make someone else do everything for you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices2">
        <item>a) Not to try and do everything carelessly.</item>
        <item>b) Try to shoot at targets.</item>
        <item>c) Shoot the commander.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices3">
        <item>a) Try to calm everyone down.</item>
        <item>b) Start fighting too.</item>
        <item>c) Do nothing.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices4">
        <item>a) Do nothing.</item>
        <item>b) Try to escape.</item>
        <item>c) Panic and disturb everyone.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices5">
        <item>a) Gather all soldiers and retreat.</item>
        <item>b) Resist until the end.</item>
        <item>c) Surrender as prisoners.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices6">
        <item>a) Gather everyone and go towards the tanks.</item>
        <item>b) Retreat and go back to the trenches.</item>
        <item>c) Hide in the forest.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices7">
        <item>a) Follow the order and retreat.</item>
        <item>b) Fight to the end.</item>
        <item>c) Try to negotiate.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices8">
        <item>a) Start shooting at them with a rifle.</item>
        <item>b) Spend ALL ammunition on them.</item>
        <item>c) Hide.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices9">
        <item>a) Try to break through the enemy defense.</item>
        <item>b) Try to sneak unnoticed behind enemy lines.</item>
        <item>c) Try to negotiate a ceasefire with the enemy.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices10">
        <item>a) Advance and attack the enemy position.</item>
        <item>b) Take defensive positions and wait for the enemy.</item>
        <item>c) Try to organize peace talks.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices11">
        <item>a) Go on a secret mission behind enemy lines.</item>
        <item>b) Participate in a sabotage operation in the enemys rear.</item>
        <item>c) Request to be assigned to a different direction.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices12">
        <item>a) Organize the defense of a key facility.</item>
        <item>b) Conduct operations to eliminate enemy command posts.</item>
        <item>c) Refuse and do nothing.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choices13">
        <item>a) Refuse.</item>
        <item>b) Agree.</item>
        <item>c) ???</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>